H hello everyone.
A warm good morning to all. Merry
Christmas.
Uh, it's past Christmas though, but
still merry Christmas to everyone. Um,
how's everyone doing? Good morning.
Hello. Hello.
Um, one second.
Uh, let me see if I'm live on YouTube.
Okay, I'm live on YouTube. Hi.
How's everyone doing? D. Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Give me a minute. Tell us check
something
bada boom bada boom. Uh,
okay. One second. Hello beha.
Hello potato.
Merry Christmas.
Hello. Hello everyone.
How is Mina doing today?
How is everyone doing?
How has life been
more?
I have a really bad um
um I have a really bad um
co uh like a co uh blocked nose today.
So, but yeah, at work and bring due to
sleeping late. Oh, no. Take care. Take
care. Just sleep only possible.
Okay. Yeah, just leave when you can.
Yeah. Today I will be playing Arc
Raidish. [laughter] You know, I will be
playing this game a lot cuz I love Arc
Raiders.
Uh, so yeah, I you know, honestly
speaking, yesterday I was supposed to
stream this game, but there's a but yes,
there's a butt.
But you know what happened? Uh,
I
slept off. I was like
feeling so tired. I Did you get
addicted? No, it's fun. Maybe I think I
don't know. It's fun game. I love uh
playing. Um it's my first time playing
an extraction shooter. No. So it it has
been really fun. Honestly speaking,
it has been really fun. Honestly
speaking. Yeah.
So
um one second. Let me just turn on all
the stuff
background applications.
All right.
All righty. And I think I should be good
to go.
Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Not [music] exactly addicted, but yeah.
You know, [laughter]
it's fun. Honestly, it's fun.
So, okay, let me uh do the Instagram
story thingy real quick. I forgot to do
this. I was supposed to stream early,
but I was like occupied with some stuff
at home like doing chores and
everything.
So, I got uh so I got um delayed to set
up stuff. Then I was in the bath
earlier. Uh so that's why we had to
delay the stream by 30 minutesish.
So,
um,
let me just get this up here and do
this.
Let me drop today's link.
Oh, yeah. How has everyone's Christmas
been? What did you do? What did you
show? What did you do? What did you get
for Christmas?
What did you guys get for Christmas?
For me, I uh wanted to do the I honestly
wanted to do a Christmas stream
um like yesterday,
but I was feeling so unwell. Plus, I
thought of like spending time with
family more.
So, I did that yesterday.
But it's all right. Like usually we used
to have like a Christmas tree thingy and
we put everyone like Christmas tree
thingy, right? That's what we used to
do.
So, and [laughter]
we couldn't do it this time this year.
But it's okay. Next year,
next year we can do it
cuz why not? Next year we have to do it
cuz I'll be alone. I wouldn't have
anyone like family or anything. So
there's that's something. Wow.
Yeah. Next year we got to do that.
[laughter]
We got to got to do that. So do you.
All right.
My throat has been really bad. So today
I'll be cleaning my room as well. My
office space. Um my stream sh stream
room.
So, um
not sure when I will be
uh getting off, but I plan to get off by
uh let's see, I I do plan to get off uh
by noon, like around uh 100 p.m. at
least
today. Uh so, I hope that goes well.
H. So, we'll have our uh one or two hour
session of araiders.
So, before this week ends, today is
Friday. I wanted to like do the trials
and complete them,
the weekly trials, right? I got to
complete them. So, we'll be focusing on
that today.
Uh I'm almost uh half a million. I got
500,000.
So, that's going good.
Uh, I'm going to get my first million
soon. I'm excited about that.
That's going to be nice.
Uh,
okay.
Oh my god, my stuff is crashing. Oh no.
Don't do this to me. Don't do this to
me.
Why are you doing this to me? Oh no.
Let me switch.
I hope everything works.
Alex says hope.
Uh, one second.
Oh, there's a Sammy update. I forgot to
update that. Oh, no.
It's fine.
Hi.
One second. Let me resist. Oh, wait.
Isn't today the new uh raider deck is
coming out or is it tomorrow?
I
completely forgot. I think it's today,
right? I think it's today. The new
winter goalie goalie uh skin.
It's a really cool skin. I would love to
have it.
For that I have to do the daily feats.
which is a bit odd, but yeah, got to do
the daily feats.
Yep. Yep. Got to do the daily feeds.
Okay, give me a minute.
This is quickly stuff.
Okay,
close this. Close this.
Uh,
>> close that and close this
probably.
One second. Give me a minute. [snorts]
Uh,
okay. This should be good enough.
All right.
Uh, my PC is lagging again. No. Oh, no.
Oh, the the new deck has not came again.
Uh, well,
well, it is what it is. uh
by Shak.
It seems to me that I cannot keep the
browser
in my background at all.
Wow.
I That's what it seems to me. Like it's
lagging. Like really lagging. [snorts]
Crazily lagging.
Okay, fine. I'll just close it.
So, let's see what is happening today.
Oh, close enough. Nice, nice, nice. Good
timing. Good timing. We have 1 [music]
hour 45 minutes [snorts] to do this. Hi.
Good timing. They all
um
Okay, good timing.
Um
All right.
35 now.
Oh yeah, there's a white chicken now.
>> Look, there's a white chicken now.
Really cool.
I got half a million.
Almost 600,000.
Really nice. Really nice.
waiting for hours.
>> I got a lot of stuff honestly.
Uh we need that.
So we will need a lot of heals.
for this run.
Yep. A lot of heals
will be needed.
>> I have a lot of recorders.
Go to the kitchen instead.
>> I think
uh
Give me a minute.
Let me drink some water.
Hydrate everyone.
Should I keep like the interactive map
on my phone and see
is that better? I think I should do
that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
met forge
update. Someone from level three swiped
the last of the fuel reserves. Hopefully
worth it.
>> Doesn't metaphor
mobile app. Does Metavor have a mobile
app?
Oh, they don't have a thing.
Uh, okay. Interesting.
>> Also,
uh, is there any traitors which are
having
uh,
>> good to see you?
Don't s you'll thank me.
>> Things are
>> only the best explosives for my favorite
raider.
>> I could take this.
>> But wait, do I have the
I don't have the blueprint. I have the
blueprint for that line. That is nice.
Uh I don't have the blueprint for
trail blazer.
I do not have it. Just need one more
rocketeer driver and I'm Gucci.
Okay. Um so if that's the case, I'll
just buy it from here.
That'll get the job done with style.
>> And uh
that will be enough,
I guess.
Okay, we'll split it into two runs.
Okay, that will be better.
That will be better. We'll split it into
two runs. So,
um
I just need a humidifier. Uh
so, we'll split the tones
for the for now. We'll focus on
harvesting plants cuz this is a bit
harder. A little bit harder. Harvest
plans and
uh destroying ticks. Maybe we could try
the leaper.
You know what? I'll try to let's do
that. We'll try to do the leaper as
well.
Where's the trail placer? Okay, with
that in my safe pocket.
Got some grenades.
Also, I don't want to lose this, so I'll
just replace it with this.
Uh, we're just going to be
we're just going to be practically
farming for the
uh trials. That's it.
That's about it.
Uh, we need the matriarch for this. Uh,
I want to get the queen and a matri, but
they didn't mind. We'll do that probably
today or tomorrow. [snorts]
Uh,
[snorts] I need bandages, right? I need
bandages.
I'm out of fabric.
I'm out of fabrics.
Yeah, I'm out of fabrics. Uh, sure. No,
no, no. That looks good.
And we would need some grenades.
I'm out of chemicals, too. Oh my god.
All right, let's go. Close up. Okay.
Okay. Let's
[snorts]
Where is the raiderish?
So depending on where we are spawning,
we'll have to do it. Okay.
I hope we are get spawned around the
north
northeast side, but northwest side is
also good.
There's a couple of stuff we can do.
Oh, my PC is dying.
Okay, swamps. Okay.
>> Hope you're clothed for the season,
Raider. It's a good day for picking
candleberries, but do beware of
frostbite.
>> Uh,
okay. We'll go here.
Someone's already loaded.
Uh, where is the
things?
I can't find the
I can't find the plants,
bro. I cannot find the plans.
Oh my god, this is bad.
Uh,
where are the plans?
Wait, this is mad. I can't find the
plants. Wait, I'm over here. I have to
I'll wait for the snow to defrost from
me
and I'll leave.
Okay, we're fully defrosted.
Hey, Raider.
>> Hey. Hello.
>> I hope this raider did not like get all
the plans. I feel like he did get the
plans.
In such cases, it will be better if I
will
>> if I could
go here.
Ah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. One,
two,
Ah, that's a player.
That's quite a few.
There's quite a few plants over here.
So, two and then this is three,
three,
four,
five.
Okay, we'll get inside this for now.
and we'll wait for the fro uh for
ourselves to get defrosted.
So, where are we? We are over here.
Uh we can go over this way the river.
Uh yeah, we're halfway there.
go through the river land and we might
find some plans.
Uh or probably not. You you never know.
Uh,
I I see some plans.
Get the plants. Come on.
Nice. Keep going. Is there any more
plans
down this way?
There should be more plants.
Ah, I see some more plants. Nice, nice,
nice.
We got these
Uh, this is not a safe space.
Um,
I will need to get myself into
some cover.
I'm starting to lose health. Oh no.
Yeah, I'm starting to lose health.
Okay, I see more flowers. I mean plants.
I shall get out
and also this.
And remember, we are not in a rush.
So, there's that as well. I am losing
tons of HP.
I would need to find a health spot.
[panting]
Also, mushrooms.
It's rare to see mushrooms, man.
Okay,
we'll do one more bandage and wait. How
much did I make it?
Oh, we got three.
Oh, we finished the challenge. Excuse
me. Wait, we finished it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. We actually
finished it. Oh, wait. I'll just get one
more.
So, we are good. Good. But yeah, we have
to do the first uh first wave husk as
well,
right? I'll also eat some lemon.
Lemon gives you more HP, I believe. No.
Oh, never mind.
Oh, yeah. Allig
actually gives you HP, it seems.
Um
the first wave house I need to find four
of them
if I am correct.
Don't get caught. Don't get caught.
Be safe.
Bus wave. Hask. Where are you?
I see some over here.
No, that's the sur weekend thingy.
Okay, leaper and first wave, right?
Okay,
we'll get we'll try to defrost and also
we need a extract far from here. No,
>> at the treatment elevator. All right.
If I could find some first wave house,
that would be really nice. Yes, I see
one.
Okay, it's not breached, so we can take
it.
We just need to search once.
We need more.
Uh there should be some around here.
Let me get into the frost.
Oh, someone's fighting the leaper.
Oh [\h__\h]
Okay.
Okay, that's nice.
She'll recharge her.
Someone's fighting the leaper. Let's go.
>> Thanks a lot. Hey, Raider.
Where are they fighting?
Ah, they destroyed the drill.
is on route.
>> I will not allow myself to die here.
>> 10 minutes to get out of there.
>> Don't shoot.
Oh, someone just destroyed it. team.
>> Hey, Raider.
>> Uh,
I need to find the
Okay, I'm taking damage.
Oh, we could reach. What if we get some
loot?
You never know.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
>> Thank you.
>> Oh my god. Nice. That was a good man.
Thanks.
All right, we'll go to the outskirts
again, I guess,
cuz I'm not seeing much past wave house.
I would like it if I could see some fast
ways.
We're halfway, man. We're halfway.
I see one.
But it's looted, right?
No, this doesn't count.
Yeah, it wouldn't count if it's looted.
I'll wait to defrost.
I'll take that. Thank you very much.
I only have 6 minutes. We have to reset.
Ah, first husk.
Okay, fine, son. I really appreciate it.
Come on.
I should do it on a different run.
I see some smoke over here.
Ah, that's an arc.
Okay,
it's better I uh leave.
Yeah, it's better I leave. I'll do it in
the next run.
Don't shoot.
>> Okay, the elevator is up. Let's go
check.
Don't shoot.
>> Is he playing music?
Is he playing music?
That guy was chilling.
The guy was chilling. Wow.
Okay. Uh,
someone helped us and gave us some
leaper pulse unit.
That was really nice. No,
we got two mushrooms and a lot of
mullins.
Oh my god. Nice. Oh my god.
My first my first first first
epic aran. A man.
Amen. Oh my god. Nice.
Okay. Doing the trials does give you
good stuff.
200 trials does give you good stuff.
No. So, we have to do the ticks. Uh,
wait. Yeah, we'll do the tick later. Uh,
we can do
the first wave house and leaper next
next this run.
Uh,
take a few bits of ammo.
And we need to craft some heels.
We need moss.
Sell us to do ammo. Thank you.
Wait, why am I getting defip? What? Why?
Huh?
Why?
I just need Andrew. Yeah. Why did I get
defect? What?
>> Forgot something.
I'll take 10 of these.
I get these over here.
Okay, this time we do leaper and fast
way husk. Okay,
let me change the thingy.
That would be the first wave
else
maybe.
>> [snorts]
>> We have to do the thick as well now.
Let's go.
We're doing good. We're really doing
well. Well, nice.
Flames free.
Oh, we got this flames spray.
Let's go.
>> Eco,
I failed statistics this year. I'm sad.
Oh no, what happened?
It's okay. You can try again next time.
How's a merry Christmas? I have no [\h__\h]
How come?
Okay, we got the same spawn as last
time. Interesting.
Okay, Arus. Correct.
>> Apollo speaking. Did you bring those
grenades, Raider? My new designs look
great on paper, but I'll need someone to
chuck them at some machines to know
anything for sure.
Arus.
I need to find a smoke key thingy.
Wherever there's a smoke, that's an arc.
My dad paid for it. Oh,
I see.
But you didn't steady. What happened
though?
But you can next time you can try to pay
for the exam yourself, you know.
Statistics is hard.
I have never done statistics, so I don't
know much about it.
Oh my god.
What do Indian people think are Chinese
people? I don't know. I I I think they
are cool. The their culture and
everything is really nice.
I can't speak for the for others. I can
only speak about myself, you know.
I still need text over here.
I almost died. Okay.
I need text.
Oh,
that's one.
holy.
Wait, I need this.
Wait, I need this. Uh
oh [\h__\h]
I cannot die.
I missed.
I got good shot.
Oh,
I missed that shot.
Oh my lord. Holy lord.
Where is it?
Duck.
I need this hornet driver, man.
Isn't it risky for me to do this?
I need an arc power shell.
I do not have an arc power shell.
Oh,
did Wait, did he shoot someone else?
Oh. Oh my god. Almost died. Wait, don't
take the rest jockn. Oh god.
Should
I be taking the risk right now? I do not
know, man.
All I know is I need this, but also
like,
[groaning]
oh [\h__\h]
Where is he?
I hear him drifting around, but
Oh [\h__\h] Oh [\h__\h]
Oh my god. Oneon one SP. Never mind.
Never mind. Don't Don't do it. Don't do
it, Jock. Don't do it. Don't do it.
It's He's not worth it.
Oh,
>> don't shoot.
>> Don't shoot.
Heat.
I need you.
Hello there.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Raider, want to team up?
>> Hey, don't shoot. Want to team up?
>> Okay.
[groaning]
Oh no, he died.
>> Let's head home at the water treatment
elevator.
Oh, he died.
What happened here?
>> Ah, he stole the rocketeer driver.
Hello.
>> Appreciate it.
>> You got any
like I have to do the leaper.
>> I am out of health.
I need to survive this.
Hey, don't shoot.
Are they extracting?
Oh, they are.
Okay, I'll just reset again.
I'm so mad at my bad something for you.
>> Enemy hang in there.
Shoot it out. Rock.
>> Hello Astra. Welcome.
Take it. Yes,
he made it. [laughter]
He made it. He slid it into the thing.
He made it. Nice.
Okay. Nice.
Let me know when you're afraid. Hi.
Yep.
>> I might be free in the evening. Not
sure. I might have to clean my room and
stuff.
My room kind of has my cat features. I
can't find where it's going. Probably
it's in the corners or under the desk or
under stuff.
Probably not sure.
Did check those places, you know.
Okay. Shotguns, shells. Uh,
okay. We need a lot of heals, man.
And I need to get my leaper.
I need to get my leaper.
Are there any Indian people who like
cracks? What do you What What is that
question? [laughter]
[gasps] I like cats. There obviously
there's going to be people who would
like cats.
[laughter] What is that question?
It doesn't make sense. Obviously,
there's going to be a lot of masses of a
lot of people who be who will be uh like
a dog person or a cat person or a bird
person who likes to have birth as pets
or cats or dogs. You never know.
Uh, [sighs]
can I recycle this or no?
I need some bandage.
Uh, [sighs]
fear of cats. Who is the 25th
chancellor? Who's that?
supply.
>> Okay. Uh
we have less time. We'll just uh do the
leaper.
Uh yeah, hund [laughter]
the leaper.
No, no, no wait, wait, wait. I need some
grenades.
I do not have chemicals.
What can I uh chemicals? Chemicals.
Uh, nope.
Can I recycle? Nope. Chemicals.
Headphones maybe. Nope.
25 of Germany. I see.
Uh,
chemicals.
I don't have much stuff. And don't die.
It's okay. It's fine.
Okay. Close enough. Come on.
We do one leaper and we wait for the
second leaper to spawn within 8 minutes.
By that time I do the
I do the this thing sticks.
We need to uh kill around eight thicks.
8 to 12 thick.
That should be enough.
I need a farm for blueprints.
We're here to farm. Where did I spawn?
I spawn in outskirts this time. H
interesting.
>> Go to the location.
>> This is Celeste speaking. Just a gentle
reminder to keep an eye out for those
salvage sites for TN. It may be just
what we need to get her to pull her
weight.
I see some smoke. Two smokes. Okay.
Okay. One.
So, we need to do seven of these.
Oh, sentinel. I need this.
Hello Vhosa.
Oh, that's the leaper,
isn't it?
Someone's fighting the leaper.
Oh, no, no, no. That's the rocketeer.
Someone's fighting the rocketeer.
What games have you bought this day? I
haven't bought anything actually.
I haven't bought much.
I bought our craters when it was not on
a sale. So, I had to spend 2,400 rupees
and I regret it. Not I don't regret it.
Like Bacon bought it on the winter sale.
So, it was just 1,900
or something.
1,800.
Uh,
but yeah, I have not been
I have not been
getting any
getting any games.
I want to get Marathon when it comes
out. I'm not sure if I'll play it cuz
I'm having fun in art creators but
marathon is like similar PV e PVP
but the issue is now it's first person
now it's like Apex.
My question is will I even play it?
You knew that sale was coming right?
Yes, I knew but the thing was I was like
I need to do the expedition. That's why
I was like,
"Yeah, I should do it." kind of thing.
Wait. Ah, Leaper. Let's go. Leaper is
here. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Okay, let's do the leaper.
Okay, let's do this.
Oh boy, I lost door.
All right. Come here. Come here. Come
here. Come here. Come here. Come here.
Oh my.
Run, run, run, run.
Oh my god, there's a [\h__\h] light.
[groaning]
Bro, what the [\h__\h] dude?
Bro,
my trail blazes.
No,
no, no, no, no, no.
Somebody help me please. Please please
help.
[screaming]
Oh, please help.
Please,
please, [laughter]
please.
Do you have a def
[laughter]
I bought 30 I bought it for 40,000
bro he ran away
at least stabilize me brother
my leaper
>> [laughter]
>> Uh, you can loot me. I'm going to die.
You can loot me,
[laughter]
bro. My drill brazer. I forgot to put it
in my safe pocket. No.
How am I going to do them? [laughter]
Why do I have a grenade?
Ah, I lost it,
man.
Ben,
[snorts] man.
Oh my god. I
I'm out of stock.
I think
>> I'm alive. What can I do?
Oh no.
Ninja pack. Oh,
got to get the snap hook.
So, that's going to be my second snap
hook, right?
Let's go. Two snap hooks.
Oh, I lost the shot. Oh my god. I lost
the good gun.
I lost the right. Oh my god. I lost the
good gun,
>> bro. I lost a good gun.
Ah.
Dang it.
God dang it.
I lost a good gun.
I don't have chemicals even to Why am I
like this?
Uh,
cannot use the bobcat. Nope.
And I lost a good amount of stuff. Why?
I lost good amount of stuff. A lot of
stuff I lost.
How often you use the gamer when you're
on your streaming? I never use that word
IRL.
I The thing is now with me, I used to
not say that much.
Um but I I think nowadays I recently
started to it somehow comes out. Usually
I have a strict rule to myself that I
will not say that gamer word.
Uh but yeah sometimes it happens I
guess. What can I say?
Uh, [groaning]
>> but I usually find um I usually find u
sensor words I could use. So I don't use
the ghost words or something.
Yeah, I'm not the type to use the gamer
word that much. So yeah,
there's that as well.
I need a shield rechargers.
Do I have that only one? Are you kidding
me right now?
Oh my god, I'm so broke.
What?
I am so broke.
Tell me and my brothers how to say it in
Chinese. Yeah. But that's crazy.
That's crazy.
>> Hello. Have merry Christmas.
5 seconds.
>> Hello. Hello.
The thing is no, the leaper I like if I
didn't lose my trailblazer over there
when that stupid hornet came in. If I
didn't die to that now, I could have
finished the leap challenge.
I wouldn't be struggling right now.
Right here.
Batman. Velp.
What can I say?
Not much stuff, huh?
Oh, goop. Goop. We got some goop.
Wait, what is that broken guidance
system?
Oh, she'll recharge it. Nice.
Lucky me.
I got time to find the leaper.
Oh, this is a fresh trade.
Uh, it is a fresh trade.
Where am I going?
Oh my god. Wait, I'll take refuse over
here.
I wasted my stamina. Okay, wait.
So, the leaper spawns are technically,
let me check,
there's four uh there's five spawn
locations. So, one is over here.
>> One is here. That's what we fought last
match. And other three are here.
>> Three spawns over there.
I will head to control tower.
Drive with it on my rear bumper. I see.
Wait, won't that won't there be a husk
over here?
I could at least finish the husk
challenge now.
There should be a husk.
Ah,
that's not a husk.
And we extract from here at the central
swamp lift.
All right.
Okay. Go.
If we are lucky, we will find a leaper.
if you're not
and it's pain.
This is not looted. No one came.
There's a raider there.
I needed the motor.
Oh [\h__\h]
Ah, I'm using the word again.
Okay, my game is lagging here and there.
That is bad.
I love you.
>> Appreciate it.
Wait, wait, that's a leaper.
Wait, that's a leaper. Someone's
fighting the leaper.
Okay, someone's fighting the leaper.
Go, go, go, go, go.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
go.
Get some damage. All you need is get
some damage.
That's it.
Oh my god.
Oh [\h__\h] This is a bad idea, man.
Stop running away.
Is it dead?
Should have taken my shotgun, man.
And I'm dying.
Oh my god. And I'm dying.
This is bad.
You're calling. Elevator is coming. Hang
in there.
Oh, bro.
Did the leaper die?
[\h__\h] hell. Oh my god.
No, [screaming]
I hate myself so much.
Hey, can you can you press the extract?
Please help.
>> Security.
Stand by.
>> Don't shoot.
I won't make it. I won't make it. I
won't make it.
Could someone bandage me, please?
Please. I'm going to die,
>> bro. No one's coming.
Go go go go go go.
>> No [\h__\h] [laughter]
Why? Why? Why?
Is it because I'm streaming? Is it
because I'm streaming?
I'm having a really bad luck.
[laughter] Oh my god.
I swear
every single time I stream
I'm having a bad luck ever though. What
the heck?
H there.
Okay, there's three days left. I know,
but
I don't have much anymore.
I lost all the good stuff, man.
And it's hard to uh kill the
And I feel like it's hard to kill the
this thing.
So where's Sentinel core?
Oh, wait. I lost this sentinel core.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Did I lose
the sentinel crew?
No,
we actually lost it.
I actually Oh my god.
No, I had one.
[crying]
Uh brother, why?
I'll have to mark you down as a regular
at this rate, my friend.
>> Uh, this sucks.
>> Or just scared of commitment.
>> I got free load out this time. Free load
out.
I cannot afford to lose anything.
Let's do the damage to text thingy.
Okay, that's better.
I'll just do that.
There's sticks in a lot of places.
We'll go by one by one. Yep. We'll go
into each the places one by one. Yeah,
that's better.
Pix can be found in indoors
spawned in the outskirts. So I have to
go
to here.
>> Move to that location.
>> It's a fresh raid.
If we do see some arc uh arc um
arc husk, I will also get that.
I see one over there.
Okay, that's one.
Uh, if we can find some shield or ammo,
that would be really good.
Oh, humidifier. I needed this.
Oh, we have to extract that.
Not now, though.
after we are done.
Ah, leaper spawned here,
man.
My game's lagging again.
Okay,
I have to get inside though.
Okay, now I need to find some ticks.
That's one.
two.
Oh my god, my PC is so boooo.
I wouldn't want to
turret.
It's just a turret. Okay.
It's not a sentinel I was looking for.
I need to find some text, man.
And we got to extract because we caught
an humidifier.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
There you go.
What a nice guy.
I think this guy is also looking for
ticks.
Where are the texts?
There should be one two ts inside this.
Somebody already came here to loot.
One take here.
Since I'm here, I might as well lure it,
I guess.
It's already looted.
>> The second deck
>> turret over here.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Second deck should be here, I think.
Wait, no one looted this. What the heck?
Okay.
Might as well extract.
I needed that.
[sighs]
Okay, there's no text here.
Okay, we have to leave.
Uh,
if there's nothing here, then the next
option is
option is over here.
>> Go to the power generation complex.
>> Is there exit?
Wait, did they already respawn?
Don't shoot.
>> Don't shoot.
>> I like how we just waved hello and went.
I feel like Stella is a good
a good
thing
for
Oh,
I like Stella is good actually.
Holy [\h__\h]
Oh my lord. Holy lord. What the heck?
And I'm out of ammo.
Oh my god.
Should I reset?
The way everything is going, it's just
telling me, Jo, just reset.
There is a chance I might see like
I might see like
uh this thing
I hear somewhere.
What will be here? Let's see.
There should be crickets here. I mean
text here,
but there isn't.
Head
home at the north complex elevator.
>> Conserve your bullets. I have to
conserve my bullets.
Oh yeah, there's definitely going to be
ticks here.
I just feel it.
Wow. Everything is looted.
Those blueprint hunters.
There's not even a single tick over
here.
What's the respawn thing?
Let me go this way.
I hear one. H.
Okay, I'm almost.
I need a little bit more.
No ticks here.
I hear X.
Oh [\h__\h]
Okay, I just need one more.
I just need one more.
I hear one. Where is it?
Just one more. Just one more.
If I lurk around here, I might
There's a chance I might lose this.
Please be text. Please let there be
text. Please let there be text.
Ah, that's a rocketeer.
>> An Arc Orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing. You have 10 minutes
to return to Spiranza. I repeat, in 10
minutes.
>> Ah, I need one, man. I just need one
more thick.
I just need one more tick.
Should I wait till it respawns?
And I desperate, desperately need some
ammo
so bad.
Maybe the other ones may have respawned.
Oh, these got respawned.
There's no X here.
I just need one, man. And I just need
one.
And I'm good to
just one.
Ah, it's not any good.
Do you think it will respawn?
Honestly, I have a bad feeling.
I really have a bad feeling.
Yes. Reset it.
Let's go. Finished it. Now we extract.
Okay,
now we extract.
Go. Run, run, run, run, run, run.
Extract.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Everything
the elevator
>> stand by.
>> All raiders, arc on screen. 5 minutes
left. Go find your way home. I repeat, 5
minutes.
Elevator up.
I hear rocket. Oh my lord, he's locked
in.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
>> Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Okay, we did the text.
Oh my god.
Hello, Bacon. Hello. Hello. I'm just
doing the trials though in uh Cole Snap.
Welcome. Welcome.
You know, I died to a stupid hornet and
I lost the three trail braces I bought
just to kill the leaper.
Ah, I lost so much though.
Okay, we finished the Oh, complex
gunpotss.
So, we finished the text.
Now we need to do the first uh first
wave arc
first wave harus and the leaper
and the raider cage
and I'll commit I'll give the humidifier
just came back from the oh what movie
did you watch. What movie did you watch?
No worries. This was enough to Oh,
nice. Nice.
So, yeah, we finished two of them. We
just need to do the frozen container
thingy. Leaper and the first wave house.
Correct. Leaper. I'll wait till tomorrow
till the
till the trader gets reseted.
>> 17 hours. No, tomorrow. I'll just do it.
Yeah. I I need to get my money back.
Yeah. So, we'll do the next run. We'll
do um
we'll do the raider cage thingy.
Oh, that's the purple one. Nice.
Ah,
I need to level up this. I need a
bombier.
Yeah, all of that needs grenades, man.
Uh,
bus wave has great. I'm halfway.
Wait, let me Should I Google this?
I need the first wave of house.
>> Also, we need to kill some sentinels as
well.
Oh yeah.
Like the best way to kill everything is
getting the blueprint for the
um
blueprint for the dust tank. The
trailblazer. This is way best ster
grenade also.
You want to have a nice place to come
home to where you can kick back and
relax
also works.
I have to kill the leaper in one go. No,
that's the hard thing. Not hard, but
yeah, I need the stuff. Okay, call
changed to here. Oh,
okay. That's a different map now.
Good Lexi Arus
Raider.
Okay, you know what? Let's do the Raider
stuff.
Seriously,
we found
Okay, we'll do a free load out. I don't
want to
uh coal snap. Yep. Let's go. So, I need
to find the raider cage.
Yeah, depending on where we are
spawning. We have to keep an eye for the
audio queue as well.
The spawn locations are a bit
random, but I'll figure something out.
Um, I'll be fine.
I was thinking of streaming in the
evening or later late night.
I'm not sure.
I got spawned over here.
>> Hope you're close with the season,
Raider. It's a good day for picking
candle, but do beware of frostbite.
>> I'm over here. No.
Wait, where am I?
Oh, spawn over. Okay, there's a rail
cage over here. Here.
>> Let's go to that location.
No.
Huh?
I don't want to hear it.
I don't think it's here.
I can't find it.
Ah, bro.
I can't find the cages.
Where are they?
>> Let's move to that location.
Am I cold or am I
defrosting? Okay, I'm defrosting.
Someone already looted all of this.
That's only candle.
Not what I needed.
and baskets.
[panting]
I finished my candle stuff.
Hey, don't shoot.
Okay. Where is the raider cages?
I'm in the parking.
Well, I can't find myself in the map.
Uh oh. Okay, I'm not supposed to be
here. Okay, we need to go.
There's some cishes over here.
damn.
What is this?
>> Don't shoot.
>> That person is crying for help.
get the back.
Holy Lord, that's a bombeter. No, that's
the
Don't shoot.
>> Oh, they're already looted.
Go kill something. Yeah, I don't have
the grenade though,
so there's no point.
I was wanting to kill it, but I don't
have the nades now.
Can I craft plastic parts?
I need some plastic pots.
Hello, Valle. Come.
We got a lot of plastic parts. I think I
can make this. I need chemicals now.
Oh my lord, I'm dead.
Why?
Don't shoot.
>> Why?
None. It's not a PVP lobby. GG.
How?
Why and how,
bro?
What the heck?
It's not a PVP, Rob. My behavior has
been so nice. Oh, why did I get queued
up with aggressive players?
Dang it.
That sucks.
You know what? I'll just go. I want to
finish the thing, but I can't finish the
thing if
you know what I'll just do raid. That'll
be better. No, I'll just get some stuff
and we'll extract.
Think that's better.
I want the purple arguments blueprint.
So yeah, we'll go do some free raids
till we get some stuff, get some money,
and then we'll
um if you're lucky, if I can get the
trailblazer blueprint, then it's good. I
can go hunt down leapers and finish the
trials
and then get the m uh get the bomber and
the sentinel and the other one as well
cuz those are also need a I need to do
those for the crafting tables. Okay,
we'll go to the seed vault.
>> Go to the seed vault.
>> It's a late raid.
Have your eyes adjusted to the dark yet.
Raider loot is ripe for the picking
while most of Toledo is asleep. Though
my suppliers say that Ark is twice as
vigilant after sunset.
Okay, it's a late raid. People have
looted
People have looted this
Uh, let's go to the containers.
>> Let's go to the lobby.
>> Lobby.
Breach. Yes.
Ah, people have loaded.
So, you get the argument the purple
blueprint from here. This kind of
container is
everyone looted everything.
Oh, that's a shredder. Oh [\h__\h]
That's Shredder. That's Shredder.
Shredder is here.
Uh, we need to go.
Oh, weapon gauge.
Uh, there's nothing much, right?
Man, we run.
We got a key, right? I'll take a key.
The heck is wrong with this?
All right.
>> Don't shoot.
Okay.
Why does it feel like the shredder is
nearby?
Hey, don't shoot.
>> Don't shoot.
Uh
reachable containers.
Hey.
>> Hey.
>> Don't shoot.
>> Hello, Raider.
>> Wait, is she shooting at me or
Ah, there's a shredder.
I honestly feel like I should extract,
but I didn't find anything. No.
>> Let's head home at the seat air.
Someone was here.
Oh, yeah. That's a
Okay. It did not spawn.
That was a dumb drop.
Oh man.
Oh, nice.
I could actually technically extract
An arc orbiter is on route. The safe
window is closing.
>> Where is the
>> 10 minutes to get out of there? I
repeat, 10 minutes.
And how do I leave this place?
Wait, how do I leave this place?
>> Go to that location.
The entrances are locked.
Oh my god. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice. Nice.
Oh my god,
that was nice blue plant. I I don't
think I had a silencer.
Hey, don't shoot.
Ah, my game is stuck. Okay, it's back.
>> All right.
Hey, don't shoot. All right.
Where is it?
Oh, it's here.
Oh [\h__\h] Oh shoot.
If it turns, if it sees me, then I'm
dead.
You know, the second expedition people
have to kill a shredder and get the core
and stuff.
That's crazy.
Oh [\h__\h] Oh no. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No.
Are these open?
Oh no. It's coming. It's coming.
Oh no. I'm I'm in a bad spot.
I'm really in a bad spot.
>> All ready. We have Ark on screen. 5
minutes left. Go find a way home. I
repeat, 5 minutes.
Please
remain.
brother.
Go go go go go go go go.
I hate the shredder so much.
It is str is like one hit kill or
something. Super hard to
super hard to kill. Woohoo.
But we got some stuff. We got a
blueprint. I already learned that. H I
can sell it then. We got a key though.
Oh god, we already learned this. Okay.
Oh, we found the Barretta, right? Oh,
yeah.
Ah, my favorite repeat. Though you're
looking surprisingly intact today.
I really do need to get the blueprint
for that.
Hey buddy, need some gear?
>> A part of me is wanting to get seeker
than this, but it won't be enough.
>> I know they don't look like much, but
you won't find better explosives
anywhere else in Toledo.
voltage converter. Ah, I Oh, no. I used
to see this before somewhere.
I need to level it. Oh god, the rocket.
Then I can do this.
Yeah, short stopper is good for stunning
stuff and like my this and that. I could
use this.
I just need one rocketeer driver.
That's a locked gate event going on.
Or should I do Stella?
We'll try to get the blueprint
blueprint for the
Bobcat or something else from the
raiders refuge. No. Or or the pilgrims
speak.
It's 12 now. I'll
What time How long am I streaming? We'll
do a short
uh Yeah, 31 minutes and we'll wrap up
for today. Okay. I got to clean up my
room and everything.
So, I've got a lot to do today.
Someone's fighting something. Someone
died.
>> Eyes on the gate. Some thugs have
triggered the emergency shutdown, which
can only be bad news. Find the key cards
to override the protocol so we can
uncover whatever it is that can't stand
the light of day.
>> Leaders refuse, right?
I think that's uh
Yeah,
that's a laborer.
Go to Raider's refuge.
Oh yeah, this is a tantr over here. No,
>> a buried mine here.
That's a mine.
Oh, someone was here.
Oh, someone died.
Hello.
Don't shoot.
>> There's not much here.
Either we search village and leave or
extra extra is there. So we can just
search village and leave I guess
everyone looted everything.
Wait, the game just started.
right now.
Okay, I really want to go here, man.
>> Okay, those guys did not see me. Nice.
Oh [\h__\h]
The stupid lag.
Come on, PC.
Why?
People
already looted this. What?
Oh my lord.
My game is lagging.
My game is lagging, bro. What the heck?
Don't know why I am carrying a rock but
okay
go.
I have this weird feeling that it's
already loaded.
That's a rocket deer.
If it was the cold snap even, no. If I I
could have came here and like
God and
Oh my god, that's two rocketeers.
Holy.
That's two of them.
We got go.
There's mines also here.
Oh my god.
Please do not tell me it's looted.
Ah, it's looted, man.
Oh, I got a key.
My game is freezing. And there
let me play.
>> Hey, don't shoot.
Oh my god, this is fully looted.
There's nothing here.
What's the point of being here?
And that's two rocketers.
The thing is, if you're not fast enough,
you won't get
a good loot.
Got to drop in. Come here. Loot,
extract.
Be lucky that you get some blueprints
and extract
a troll car. Okay, we got two keys.
Bro, some someone was here.
Someone was here. Oh my god.
Sneaky trap. I saw the shop and I walked
straight into it. No.
volcanic.
>> Come on, Raiders.
>> Don't shoot.
>> System override in clearance pending.
Standby.
Okay. They are like expedition one
players as well.
>> Yeah. Let's boogie.
[laughter]
That might scan us.
Oh, it's gone.
We didn't get much. That's one thing.
I didn't get much. Oh,
I don't know why my PC is struggling.
Wow.
I'm feeling hungry. I'll just wrap up
and go eat. We'll stream again the
evening
if possible.
Like I need a clear clearing up some
space
poster.
I have so many raider hatch keys.
Nice.
Oh, I have one trailblazer. Oh,
I'll save it. Let's save it.
I don't care.
>> Come on in, friend.
Okay,
come play security.
What?
I need to finish off these damn keys.
Damn surveillance keys. Actually,
it's better to go when it's cold snap or
like thunder
event
so I could like
get the good loot and extract, you know,
H
every
wasp the I work.
I need one more rest gear now.
Yeah, one more rest gear.
Advanced mechanical components. Yep.
Surveyor bolt.
Rocketeer. Bombardier.
Bastion.
Secure the checkpoint room.
Blow controller to
flow controller.
Wait, I think I've seen that before. Uh,
flow control. I need to find that now.
Stellar.
Hum. Hum.
Oh, this is 15k. Okay.
Damn. Okay.
10k. Um 61.2. Okay. We'll do that.
Great. We'll do though
um this thing um like later tonight I
guess. Yeah. Yeah.
Hi. I'll just uh wrap up for now. I'll
play it again. All right. We'll play the
game again later. a wrap up for today.
I
I'll have to clean up my room and
everything, so I'll have to do work on
that.
Hi.
Uh, we will up a book.
I need to figure out a way to play this
game where I won't be lagging. Like I am
running a really really light setup and
still I'm lagging in this game as in
when I stream whenever only whenever I
stream okay
the game is not handling it
and yeah it is it is such a pain.
One second.
Okay. Already guys see my attend always
my channel.
Let me just do this.
Today was fun. I really did. And also I
noticed one thing. Whenever whenever I
sit down to stream
this game, I have a bad luck. But when
I'm not sitting down and streaming this
game, I have a good luck. Is that
normal? I do not know.
And it's super weird,
too.
Super super weird though.
Yeah.
Uh
anyway, we'll uh rain my channel and um
we'll wrap it up for here.
Hi. Anyway, thank you for watching
today. Hope you enjoyed today. Thank
you. I'm a warm merry Christmas to all
for those uh who are still having
Christmas. So yeah. Hi. I will see you
guys in the evening or maybe tomorrow.
Hi.
Bye-bye. Have a great great